

Contact

Current Address: 27 Ngozi Avenue, Aba, AB. Poly Junction Road, Owerri 07013978510 (Mobile) darlingtonokoriec@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ darlingtonokoriec (LinkedIn)

www.facebook.com/ darlingtonokoriec (facebook)

www.github.com/ darlingtonokoriec (GitHub)

Top Skills

PHP

LARAVEL

Javascript Jquery Wordpress Codelgniter(Working Proficiency)

Spoken Languages

Spanish (Limited Working)
English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Facebook Blueprint
Innovation Growth Hub Certification
Google Digital Skills
Jobberman Certification
SideHustle certification
Wrtiter's Hub certification

Honors-Awards

Award of Merit, Volunteer, Vision Alive Foundation

Darlington Okorie

A Web Developer with three years of experience, and a Content Creator.

Nigeria

About Me

I am a web developer specifically on the Laravelphp framework, a writer, tech trainer and certified marketing expert.

As a software developer, I am proficient with the Javascript and PHP programming language PHP with Laravel for backend web development.

Experience

The Free School Foundation Web Developer December 2021 - 2022 (Till Present) Built www.thefreeschoolfoundation.org

Jumandi Inc Web Developer January 2021 - 2022 (Till Present)

Pan-African Spark
Assistant Chief Technology Officer
September 2020 - 2021 (1 year, 2 months)
Page 1 of 3

ECC Consults, Nigeria Software Engineer March 2020 - 2021 (1 year) Port Harcourt, Rivers, Nigeria

I worked to build software products for budding brands, connecting clients with their ideal users.

Sanstonz Technical Trainer March 2019 - 2021 (2years 2 month) Abuja, Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria

I train business owners to build their digital presence using global standards tools as specified by Google Digital Skills Africa

Vision Incubation Hub Senior Web Developer August 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 2 months) Built www.visionalivefoundation.org

Built software solutions using WordPress for Vision Incubation Hub and as well as for their clients.

Vision Alive Foundation Chief Technology Officer June 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 4 months) Aba

I worked with Vision Alive Foundation in organizing projects through software and through technology tools.

Google
Google YDDP Project
March 2019 - August 2019 (6 months)
Aba, Abia, Nigeria

I worked as a field researcher to carry out survey in order to build products for teams in Aba

Innovation Growth Hub 8 months Intern January 2019 - August 2019 (8 months) Junior Software Developer January 2019 - April 2019 (4 months) Aba

Famevive Tech Institute Software Developer April 2019 - June 2019 (3 months) Aba

Facebook My Business Technical Trainer March 2018 - April 2019 (1 year 2 months) Nigeria

Helped young business owners get into having a robust online presence for their business.

Education

Citi Polyechnic, Dawaki, Abuja OND, Business Admin and Management · (2021 - present)

Personal Projects

React/ NODEJs

Covid-Tracker

A covid19 Tracker app built on ReactJs by connecting he API of Covid19 database.

https://mystifying-wing-08fefe.netlify.app/

React/ NODEJs

Bloggerman

A blog built on the NodeJs, Expressjs framework, implementing method_override https://mi-messageboard.herokuapp.com/

VueJs/ NODEJs

MessageBoard

A message blog built with VueJs on the NodeJs, Expressjs framework https://heuristic-perlman-e98b8e.netlify.app/#/
React/ NODEJs

Laravel Projects for Clients

(Unless Expired)

Oceanworld is built on the Laravel framework https://oceanworld.com.ng/
Biscrap, a crypto currency website https://biscrap.com
Jumandi: A cooking gas booking website. (To be shared on linkedin)

For a more up to date list of my personal projects, please visit my linkedin @ https://linkedin.com/in/darlingtonokoriec